Guide to the Stanford University, Native American Cultural Center, Records SC1228
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Native American Cultural Center records
1973-2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Native American Cultural Center
SC1228
12.25 Linear Feet 12 boxes
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical / Historical
The mission of the Native American Cultural Center is to improve the quality of life for American Indians, Alaska Natives, Native Hawaiians, and Indigenous Pacific Islanders. The Center reaches out to new students and their families to help them adjust to life at Stanford - to help them realize goals and prepare for the future.
The Native American Community at Stanford dates back earlier than the institution itself. Built on land originally inhabited by the Muwekma Ohlone Tribe, Stanford University opened its doors in 1891. Three years later, John Milton Oskison was the first Native American to graduate from Stanford. Fueled by the spirit of social and political change during the 1960's, a group of Native students worked with the university administration to increase educational opportunities for Natives at Stanford. Since then, Native American numbers have increased, and students have continued to take an active role in increasing opportunities for our community at Stanford. Today, there are more than 325 undergraduate and graduate students representing more than 50 tribes studying at Stanford.
Stanford University. Native American Cultural Center
- Audiovisual material, 1973-2014
  - Hanitchak Lecture - Stephanie Fryberg, 2003-02-19; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Hanitchak Lecture - James Leckie, 2003-04-30; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Hanitchek Lecture - John Rick - Stanford History, 2004-02-18; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Hanitchak Lecture - Nancy Mithlo, 2004-11-03; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Hanitchak Lecture - Ned Blackhawk, 2005-02-16; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Hanitchak Lecture - Torsten Kjelgstrand, 2005-04-20; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Hanitchak Lecture - Summer Waggonner Fenerman, 2005-11-16; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Muwekma-Ohlune Presentation, 2001-11-14; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Manuel Jordan, 2002-02-13; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Nancy Mithlo Lecture, 2004-11-03; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Native American Speaker Series - Kenric Tsethlikai, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Shaun Anthony Roman - Memorial Service, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Alumni Hall of Fame Induction, 38646; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Hall of Fame Ceremony, 37912; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Alumni Hall of Fame Ceremony, 38282; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Multicultural Hall of Fame Ceremony, 37547; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Unidentified, undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Alumni Dinner, 36820; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Native American Alumni Dinner, 38647; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Native American Indian Organization - 40th Anniversary Celebration, 2010; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 1)
  - First Nations' Institute Opening Ceremony, 2007; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 1)
  - Native American Indian Organization - Mentor Dinner, 2011; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 1)
  - Research Forum - Honoring Native Scholarship, 1995-04-08; 4 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Research Forum, 1996-04-13; 5 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Research Forum, 1997-04-12; 4 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Research Forum *no part 2 of 5*, 3/7/1998 - 3/8/1998; 4 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Research Forum, 1999-04-10; 4 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Research Forum, 2000-04-01; 4 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Research Forum, 2001-04-28; 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Native American Research Conference, 2006-04-28; 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Native American Research Forum, 2012; 2 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 2)
  - 4th Annual Bay Area Native American Research Conference, 2009; 2 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 2)
  - Muekma-Ohlone Presentation, 2001; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Center Dinner Tony Reyna, 2004; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Navajo Nation Supreme Court Oral Arguments, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Peacemaking Demonstration, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Rufus Good Striker, 1991; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Manuel Jordan, 2002-02-13; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - 23rd Annual Stanford Powwow & Cinco de Mayo Celebration, 1994; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - 25th Annual Stanford Powwow, 1996; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - 29th Annual Stanford Powwow - Tape #2, 2000; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - 29th Annual Stanford Powwow - Tape #4, 2000; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - SAIO 20th Anniversary Week, 1990; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Real Indian/With Clean Hands and Straight Eyes, undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Real Indian, 1996; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Thompson Totem Pole for Stanford, undated; 3 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Muwekma Seminar Tony Reyna, 2004-01-26; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Giovanna Papunetti Lecture, 2004-01-28; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Don's Interview, 21st Centure Native American, 1992; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Demort Visiting Scholar/Horace Poolaw Project, undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Greg Sarris Lecture at Bolinas Museum, 1993; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Sounds of Faith, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Graduation
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (1993), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (1995), 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (1998), 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (1999), 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2000), 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2001), 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2002), 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2003), 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2004), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2005), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2006), 2 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2007), 2 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2008), 2 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2009), 2 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2010), 2 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2011), 2 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2012)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2013), 2 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Graduation (2014), 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
  - Language Instruction
    - Lakota-Souix, 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakota-Souix Session 6-7, 4/10/73 and 4/15/73; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 1, Lesson 1 - Conversation Drill 1, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 2, Lesson 1 - Pronunciation Drills 1-4, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 3, Lesson 1 - Pronunciation Drills 5-8, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 4, Lesson 1 - Grammar Drills 1 and 2, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 5, Lesson 2 - Conversations 1 and 2, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 6, Lesson 2 - Conversations 2 and 3, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 7, Lesson 2 - Pronunciation Drills 1-5, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 8, Lesson 2 - Pronunciation Drills 6 and 7, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 9, Lesson 2 - Grammar Drills 1 and 2, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 10, Lesson 2 - Pronunciation Drills 6 and 7, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 11, Lesson 2 - Grammar Drills 3-6, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 12, Lesson 2 - Long Dialogue, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101, Tape 13, Lesson 2 - Questions, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 14 Lesson 3: Conversation Drill 1, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 15 Lesson 1: Pronunciation Drills 1-3, 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 16 Lesson 3, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 17 Lesson 3, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 18 Lesson 3, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 19 Lesson 3, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 20 Lesson 3, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 21 Lesson 3, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101, Lesson 3 - Short Conversations, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 22 Lesson 4, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 23 Lesson 4, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 24 Lesson 4, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 25 Lesson 4, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 26 Lesson 4, 1973-74; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakhota 101 Tape 28, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 4-6, 27400; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 7-9, 27400; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 10-12, 27400; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 13-15, 27400; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 16-18, 27400; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 19-21, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 22-23, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 24-29, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 30-35, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 36-44, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 45-53, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 54-59, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Master Navajo 60-64, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Navajo Interview Master, 27374; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - CREE 1/2, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - CREE 3/4, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - CREE 5/6, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - CREE 7/8, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - CREE 9/10, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Cree Side 1, 27668; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Cree Side 2, 27668; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Cherokee 1,2,3 (1973), 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakota Souix (1973), 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakota Souix, Session 8 (1973), 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakota Souix, Sesson 9 (1973), 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakota Souix, Session 10 (1973), 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakota Souix, Session 11 (1973), 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Lakota Souix, Session 12 (1973), 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Cherokee Bilingual Educ. Program, 26676; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Blackfoot Tape 1, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Blackfoot Tape 2, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Blackfoot 3 & 4, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Blackfoot Side 1, 27685; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Blackfoot Side 2, 27685; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
    - Blackfoot, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lak #29, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota Civil Rights 1, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Lakhota Civil Rights 2, undated; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
    - Navajo Made Easier (1974), 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
- Newsletters, 1974-2010
  - Humming Arrows, 1974-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - CampCrier, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Story Teller, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Coming Voice, 1989-2010 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
- Photographs
  - group photo, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - photos of Nicole Stern, Raymond John, Dabah Dobrinen, Chris Peters, Cheryl Kettell, Ronalda Cadiente, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - photos of Stan Rakestraw, Leonard Bauer, Ann Smith, Chris Atcitty, Linda Tiaokasin, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - AISIP 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - photo of pair in traditional garm, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - AISIP 1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - photos of Ken Attocknie, Leo Barlow, Berni Begay, John Evans, Jim Isturis, Nona Keevama, Debbie Lamebull, Alive Ledbetter, Ron Lomahaftewa, Sarah Seeberger, Lorenzo Stars, Elaine Thomas, Pauline Tsosie, Sue Turnbull, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - photos of Martha Anagick, Elizabeth Garza, Paul Groves, Al Harris, James Howell, Kathy Jefferson, Steve June, Price Leavitt, Ethel Patkotak, Cindy Patterson, Larry Rodgers, Cathy See, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - photos of Thomas Pratt, Regina Holyan, Willard Harris, Robert Shilling, Kellie Elliott, Gary Nez, Ben Attencio, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - AISIP 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - AISIP 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - AISIP 1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - AISIP 1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - AISIP 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - AISIP 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 22nd Annual Stanford Powwow, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - photos of Steve Begay, Emmaline Black Elk, Carol Cypher, Martha Descheenie, Steve Garrison, Irvin Harrison, Anita Jackson, Jasper Joe, Agatha Knox, Marlene Laclair, Gloria Navakuku, Sarah Sneed, Ev Tucker, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - photos of Chris Cole, John Derryberry, Tammy English, Andrew Haff, Anneliese Heyl, Chris Irwin, Marlene Jones, Tracy LeBeau, Ken Lewis, Todd Michael, Jeff Patrick, Joseph Schepise, Ralinda Tate, Tammy Voss, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 9 photo collages of various people, 1975-1992 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Native American Artwork (Rob Billin), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - photos of Sharon Malotte, Hartman Lomawaima, Robert Stearns, Judy Wellington, Albert Rinehart, Larry Echo Hawk, Mark Wauahdooah, Rencie Eteeyan, Dennis Little, Billy Bear, 1969-1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - photos of Wilson, Sequoyah, Parent, Kane, Neeley, Yeltatzie, Liard, Montoya, Belgarde, Nordstrand, Hagen, Michael, Campbell, Stern, Last, Vitacca, Haddock, Ardito, Williams, Studebaker, Smith, Sandoval, Thompson, Kettell, Etsitty, Redner, Sandoval, Dutcher, Kerrigan, Flies-Away, White Eyes, Cable, Burrell, Ghahate, Haven, Gleason, Haddock, 1972-1992 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - photos of Nora Greaves, Nila Romero, Mike Johnston, Karen Atkinson, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - photos of T. Gleason, J. Kookesh, S. Rijken, M. Funston, Marie Garrison, Claudia Basham, Tonya Campbell, Laurence Brown, Danny Ammon, Anne-Marie Sargent, Maxine Alex, Tracy LeBeau, Cassandra Nordstrand, 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - photos of Dybdahl, Funston, Williams, Sommer, Jackson, Michael, Parker, Attocknie, Gover, Bourelle, McCabe, Dybdahn, Belgarde, Culbertson, Ruel, Ruel, Hately, Kroll, Alstrom, John, Michael, Michael, Stern, Ardito, Michael, Belgarde, Kettell, Haven. Kookesh, Parker, Dybdahl, Attocknie, Masayesva, Begay, Michael, SAIO 20th Anniversary Alumni Reunion 1990, 1986-1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - photos of Raymond John, Leona Wicks, Travis Michael, Notah Begay, Shawna Valenta, Brian Baker, Diane Vigil, James Larimore, Williams, Attocknie, Gover, Belgarde, Lee, Traylor, Dybdahl, McCabe, Bourelle, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - photos of John Lewis, Irene Folstrom, Travis Michael, Chris O'Garman, Nicky Michael, Raymond John, Paula Dybdahl, Jaeleen Kookesh, Kate Lupton, Theresa Matt, 1988-1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - photos of McCabe, Begay, Bray, Oakes, Ammon, Jeanne, Masaysva, Pahmahmie, Roman, Thomas, Hamilton, Cram, Chavers, Green, Moquino, Williams, Begay, McCabe, Begay, Cram, Masayesva, McCabe, Oakes, Bray, Begay, Thomas, McCabe, Jeanne, Williams, Pahmahmie, Cram, Hamilton, Ammon, Pahmahmie, Masayesva, Williams, Begay, Thomas, Jeanne, McCabe, Green, McCabe, Begay, Moquino, Chavers, Green, Roman, Ammon, Thomas, Chavers, Moquino, Begay, Hamilton, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - photos of Danielsen, Agoyo, Heitman, Kinsel, Ross, Rijken, Mithlo, West, Sage, Shelton, Demmert, Ferguson, Pipestem, Pond, Maclean, Tompkins, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - photos of Begay, Agoyo, Young, Kookesh, Lee, Gleason, Moquino, Noms, McCabe, Ruel, Pipestem, Cooke, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - photos of Hamilton, Carlson, Sekaquaptewa, Yellowman, Chun, Fryberg, Hill, Chief, Attocknie, Smith, Chavez, Lukin, Aldecoa, Flores, Uttelain, Parker, Begay, Aloysius, Tate, Abarr, Hill, Parker, Lukin, Perry, Lee, Jeanne, Wellman, Martine, Monroe, Glenn, North, Lee, Kinsel, Sutton, Valdo, Jumping Eagle, 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - photos of Matthew, Downey, Williams, Horse Grant, Begaye, Begay, Littlesalt, Gilmore, Jacobsen, Jamias, Horsen, Tsosie, Begay, Reyhner, Whiteman-Runs, Kitka, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Posters, 1983-2014
  - War Bonnets, Tin Lizzies, and Patent leather Pumps: Kiowa Culture in Transition, 1925-1955; The Photographs of Horace Poolaw, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Powwow, 2003-2014 (Box 6)
  - Tribal Strength Through Education, undated (Box 6)
  - One With the Earth, 1983 (Box 6)
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2015-125
  - Stanford Powwow program, 2013 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-315
  - American Indian Summer Immersion Program photographs, 1992-1993 (Box 1)